{
 "subject": "economics",
 "lesson": "l01",
 "grade": "c8",
 "quests": [
	{
		"id": 1,
		"question": "Which metals were used for metallic money?",
		"options": {
			"a": "gold",
			"b": "silver",
			"c": "bronze",
			"d": "all the above"
		},
		"answer": "d"
	},
	{
		"id": 2,
		"question": "Who designed the symbol (`) of Indian 	rupee?",
		"options": {
			"a": "Udayakumar",
			"b": "Amartya Sen",
			"c": "Abijith Banerjee",
			"d": "None of these"
		},
		"answer": "a"
	},
	{
		"id": 3,
		"question": "The value of money is",
		"options": {
			"a": "Internal value of money",
			"b": "External value of money",
			"c": "Both a & b",
			"d": "None of these"
		},
		"answer": "c"
	},
	{
		"id": 4,
		"question": "Which is the Bank Money?",
		"options": {
			"a": "Cheque",
			"b": "Draft",
			"c": "Credit and Debit cards",
			"d": "All the above"
		},
		"answer": "a"
	},
	{
		"id": 5,
		"question": "Pick out the incorrect one: Investment can be made in different 	vehicle.",
		"options": {
			"a": "Stock	",
			"b": "Bonds",
			"c": "Mutual fund",
			"d": "Pay tax"	
		},
		"answer": "d"
	},
	{
		"id": 6,
		"question": "Among the following who are responsible for Black Money?",
		"options": {
			"a": "Tax evaders",
			"b": "Hoaders",
			"c": "Smugglers",
			"d": "All of the above"
		},
		"answer": "d"
	},
	{
		"id": 7,
		"question": "Barter system",
		"options": {
			"a": "tax evaders",
			"b": "Electronic Money",
			"c": "Consumer’s disposable income",
			"d": "exchanged goods for goods"
		},
		"answer": "d"
	},
	{
		"id": 8,
		"question": "Reserve Bank act",
		"options": {
			"a": "tax evaders",
			"b": "1935",
			"c": "Consumer’s disposable income",
			"d": "exchanged goods for goods"
		},
		"answer": "b"
	},
	{
		"id": 9,
		"question": "E- Money",
		"options": {
			"a": "tax evaders",
			"b": "Electronic Money",
			"c": "Consumer’s disposable income",
			"d": "exchanged goods for goods"
		},
		"answer": "b"
	},
	{
		"id": 10,
		"question": "Savings",
		"options": {
			"a": "tax evaders",
			"b": "Electronic Money",
			"c": "Consumer’s disposable income",
			"d": "exchanged goods for goods"
		},
		"answer": "c"
	},
	{
		"id": 11,
		"question": "Black money",
		"options": {
			"a": "tax evaders",
			"b": "Electronic Money",
			"c": "Consumer’s disposable income",
			"d": "exchanged goods for goods"
		},
		"answer": "a"
	}	}
  ]
}